{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Garage Remodeling Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40130/":{"taskOID":40130,"originalTaskOID":40130,"setID":441,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7686,"questionDisplayText":"Scope of Remodel","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes this garage remodel?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":200666,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Completely remodel garage","answerDisplayText":"Completely remodel garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200667,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Organize garage space","answerDisplayText":"Organize garage space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200668,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Enlarge existing garage","answerDisplayText":"Enlarge existing garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20616,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Build a new garage","answerDisplayText":"Build a new garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7688,"questionDisplayText":"Storage cabinets / shelving","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Storage cabinets / shelving","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7687,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20619,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to add or update the cabinets / shelving","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to add or update the cabinets / shelving","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20620,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to add or update the cabinets / shelving","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to add or update the cabinets / shelving","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7745,"questionDisplayText":"Garage doors","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Garage doors","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7687,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20804,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the garage doors","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the garage doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20805,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the garage doors","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the garage doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7689,"questionDisplayText":"Insulation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Insulation","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7687,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20621,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to add insulation","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to add insulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20622,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to add insulation","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to add insulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7690,"questionDisplayText":"Flooring","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Flooring","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7687,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20623,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the flooring","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20624,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the flooring","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7691,"questionDisplayText":"Electrical","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Electrical","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7687,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20625,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the lighting or electrical fixtures","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the lighting or electrical fixtures","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20626,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the lighting or electrical fixtures","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the lighting or electrical fixtures","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7695,"questionDisplayText":"Interior walls or drywall","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Interior walls or drywall","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7687,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":200740,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to add or remove walls or drywall","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to add or remove walls or drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200741,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to add or remove walls or drywall","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to add or remove walls or drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503473,"questionDisplayText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","shortQuestionText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7686,"questionDisplayText":"Scope of Remodel","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes this garage remodel?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":200666,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Completely remodel garage","answerDisplayText":"Completely remodel garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200667,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Organize garage space","answerDisplayText":"Organize garage space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200668,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Enlarge existing garage","answerDisplayText":"Enlarge existing garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20616,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Build a new garage","answerDisplayText":"Build a new garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":200666,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Completely remodel garage","answerDisplayText":"Completely remodel garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200667,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Organize garage space","answerDisplayText":"Organize garage space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200668,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Enlarge existing garage","answerDisplayText":"Enlarge existing garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20616,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Build a new garage","answerDisplayText":"Build a new garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7688,"questionDisplayText":"Storage cabinets / shelving","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Storage cabinets / shelving","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7687,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20619,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to add or update the cabinets / shelving","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to add or update the cabinets / shelving","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20620,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to add or update the cabinets / shelving","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to add or update the cabinets / shelving","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20619,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to add or update the cabinets / shelving","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to add or update the cabinets / shelving","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20620,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to add or update the cabinets / shelving","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to add or update the cabinets / shelving","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7745,"questionDisplayText":"Garage doors","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Garage doors","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7687,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20804,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the garage doors","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the garage doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20805,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the garage doors","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the garage doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20804,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the garage doors","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the garage doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20805,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the garage doors","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the garage doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7689,"questionDisplayText":"Insulation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Insulation","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7687,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20621,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to add insulation","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to add insulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20622,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to add insulation","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to add insulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20621,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to add insulation","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to add insulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20622,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to add insulation","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to add insulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7690,"questionDisplayText":"Flooring","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Flooring","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7687,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20623,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the flooring","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20624,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the flooring","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20623,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the flooring","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20624,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the flooring","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7691,"questionDisplayText":"Electrical","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Electrical","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7687,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20625,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the lighting or electrical fixtures","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the lighting or electrical fixtures","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20626,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the lighting or electrical fixtures","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the lighting or electrical fixtures","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20625,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to update the lighting or electrical fixtures","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to update the lighting or electrical fixtures","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20626,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to update the lighting or electrical fixtures","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to update the lighting or electrical fixtures","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7695,"questionDisplayText":"Interior walls or drywall","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Interior walls or drywall","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":7687,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":200740,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to add or remove walls or drywall","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to add or remove walls or drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200741,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to add or remove walls or drywall","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to add or remove walls or drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":200740,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to add or remove walls or drywall","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to add or remove walls or drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200741,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to add or remove walls or drywall","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to add or remove walls or drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503473,"questionDisplayText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","shortQuestionText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"__cache./api/resource/task/40130/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40130,"taskName":"Garage - Remodel","taskDescription":"Remodel a Garage","xmTaskDescriptor":"Garage Remodeling Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":96,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Garage addition remodeling bedroom car","textMessagingName":"Remodel Garage","rolloverLongDesc":"These firms are general contractors who build or remodel garages. They supply or coordinate all the relevant services including framing, masonry, HVAC, electrical, drywall, etc.","rolloverShortDesc":"Professionally build attached or detached garage.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Remodel a Garage .  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Garage Remodel \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Renovate Your Garage","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":2,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Garage Remodel","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Garage - Remodel","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Garage Remodeling Project","urlName":"Garage-Remodel","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Garage Remodel Companies - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Garage,addition,remodeling,bedroom,car,tool,renovation,conversion,remodel,general,contractor,finish","emcCategoryOid":-12001,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":441,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}